Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1891-2012; 188.25 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons and 139 oversize flat boxes
  - Subseries I.B: Communication Workers, 1914-2012; 32 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons and 32 oversize flat boxes
    - Bulletin of the Correlated Graphic Industries, inc: Correlated Graphic Industries, New York, NY, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Critical Times: Critical Times Newspaper Collective - New American Movement, Philadelphia, PA, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Write Up: Detroit-Metro Chapter UPSurge, Detroit, MI, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - AUTW News Bulletin: Editorial Department of the American Union of Telephone Workers, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Horizons '76: Educational and Cultural Fund of the Electrical Industry, Flushing, NY, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Our Industry's Mosaic: Educational and Cultural Fund of the Electrical Industry, Flushing, NY, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - A.P. Review: Employees of the Associated Press, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Unidad: Federacion de Trabajadores Telefonicos de Cuba en el Exilio, Miami, FL, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - FTR News: Federal Telephone and Radio Corporation, Newark, NJ, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Final Warning: Final Warning, New York, N.Y., 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Guild Voice: Gary Newspaper Guild, Gary, IN, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Working People's Voice: Graphic Communications International Union, New York, NY, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper Worker: Inter-American Federation of Working Newspapermen's Organizations, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - IBEW: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Local Union Directory: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Washington, DC, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Utility Reporter: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers - Local Union 1245, Walnut Creek, CA, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Reporter: International Labor Communications Association, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Appeal: International Typographical Union - New York Local No. 6, New York, NY, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Bulletin (Supplement): International Typographical Union, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Pension Plan: International Typographical Union, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - I.T.U. News: International Typographical Union - Executive Council, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - ITU Review: International Typographical Union - Executive Council, Colorado Springs, CO, 1965, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - ITU Review: International Typographical Union - Executive Council, Colorado Springs, CO, 1964-1984 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
    - IUE-CWA News: International Union of Electric, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers - Communication Workers of America, Washington, DC, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - History and Organization of the Joint Industry Board of the Electrical Industry: Joint Industry Board of the Electrical Industry, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Los Angeles Guildsman: Los Angeles Newspaper Guild - Local 69, Los Angeles, CA, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Memo to Mailers: Memo to Mailers, Washington, DC, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Detroit Union: Metropolitan Detroit Council of Newspaper Unions, Detroit, MI, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Metrospect: Metropolitan New York Labor Press Council, New York, NY, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Tie Lines: Michigan Bell, Detroit, MI, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Newsletter: Mid-Altantic Conference of Printers and Mailers, Baltimore, MD, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - The Ring Knife: Missoula, Montana Postal Workers, Missoula, MT, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - L'Aiguilleur: la voix de l'ACWA: Montreal Joint Board of the ACWA, Montreal, Canada, 1952-1958, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - L'aiguille: Montreal Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (CLC-AFL-CIO), Montreal, Canada, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Guild Bulletin: Montreal Newspaper Guild, Montreal, Canada, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - POV (NABET 15): National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians - Local 15, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Local 15 In Focus: National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians - Local No. 15, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Bulletin: National Association of Letter Carriers, Washington, DC, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Capitol Notes / National Association of Letter Carriers: National Association of Letter Carriers, Washington, DC, 1980-1984 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Postmark Washington: National Association of Letter Carriers, Washington, DC, 1985-1988 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - NALC Activist Cumulative Index: National Association of Letter Carriers Information Center, Washington, DC, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Postal Transport Journal: National Postal Transport Association, Washington, DC, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Progressive: National Postal Union, Washington, DC, 1959, 1961-1971 (Box 3, Folder 34, Box 150, Folder 11-12, Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Spotlight: New York Newspaper Guild - Rank & File of the New York Newspaper Guild, New York, NY, 1949, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Strike Update: New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union - No. 2, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Number Six Bulletin: New York Typographical Union, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Typographical Union: New York Typographical Union - No. 6, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Guild News: Newspaper Guild (AFL-CIO), Philadelphia, PA, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Let's Talk Shop: Newspaper Guild Consumers Union Unit, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Guilder: Newspaper Guild of Albany, NY, Albany, NY, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Guild Memo: Newspaper Guild of Detroit Local 22, AFL-CIO, Detroit, MI, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Guild Memo: Newspaper Guild of Detroit Local 22, AFL-CIO, Detroit, MI, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Local 3 Bulletin: Newspaper Guild of New York, 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - New York Guildpaper: Newspaper Guild of New York, New York, NY, 1942-1944, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Speaking Up: Newspaper Guild of New York - American Journal of Nursing, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - City Desk: Newspaper Guild of New York - Amsterdam News Unit, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Guild Brooklyn Eagle: Newspaper Guild of New York - Brooklyn Eagle Unit, New York, NY, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Talk of 42nd St.: Newspaper Guild of New York - Daily News Unit, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Hot Tips!: Newspaper Guild of New York - Daily Racing Form, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - El Diario-La Prensa Guild Bulletin: Newspaper Guild of New York - El Diario-La Prensa Unit, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Watch on the Raritan: Newspaper Guild of New York - New Brunswick Home News Unit, 1979, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Times Topics: Newspaper Guild of New York - New York Times Unit, 1975, 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Union Times: Newspaper Guild of New York - New York Times Unit, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Tribune Times: Newspaper Guild of New York - News Tribune Unit, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - News Angles: Newspaper Guild of New York - News Unit, 1971, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - News Shop Paper: Newspaper Guild of New York - News Unit, New York, NY, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Newsweek Guild Bulletin: Newspaper Guild of New York - Newsweek Unit, 1980, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - News Unlimited: Newspaper Guild of New York - Post Unit, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - South St. Other: Newspaper Guild of New York - Post Unit, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Guildside: Newspaper Guild of New York - Republican-American Unit, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Common Sense: Newspaper Guild of New York - Reuters Unit, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Facts and Forum: Newspaper Guild of New York - Scholastic Unit, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Spotlight: Newspaper Guild of New York - Standard & Poor's Unit, circa 1970s (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Guild Telegram and Sun: Newspaper Guild of New York - World-Telegram and Sun Unit, New York, NY, 1950 (Box 87, Folder 3, Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Truth: Newspaper Guild of New York - World-Telegram Unit, New York, NY, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Guild Progressive: Newspaper Guild of NYC - Independent Progressive Members of the Newspaper Guild of NYC, New York, NY, 1940 (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Byline: Newspaper Reporters Association, New York, NY, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Spark: NJ-NJ United Workers Organization Electrical Committee, New York, NY, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - APT Connections: North Carolina Department of Administration - Agency for Public Telecommunications, Raleigh, NC, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Work Life: Ohio Bell, Cleveland, OH, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Pacific Northwest Newspaper Guild: Pacific Northwest Newspaper Guild, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - PLP Flash: People's Labor Party, Cambridge, MA, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Back Grounder: Portland Newspaper Guild, Portland, ME, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Postal Action: Bulletin of the Postal Action Committee: Postal Action Committee, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - "The Struggle Continues:" Address by Jean-Claude Parrot, National President, Canadian Union of Postal Workers: Postal Workers Defense Committee, Jersey City, NJ, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Fight for a Good Contract: Postal Workers for a Good Contract, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Postal Workers Voice: Postal Workers Voice, Hoboken, NJ, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Postal Workers Voice: Postal Workers Voice, Hoboken, NJ, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Postal Bulletin: Postmaster General, Washington, DC, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 1212 News: Radio, TV and Broadcast Engineers, Local 1212 IBEW, AFL-CIO, New York, NY, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Rank and File Postal Worker: Rank and File Postal Worker, Philadelphia, PA, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - On Strike, Shut It Down: San Francisco State Strike Committee, circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Bay Guild News: San Francisco-Oakland Newspaper Guild, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Bay Guildsman: San Francisco-Oakland Newspaper Guild, San Francisco, CA, 1958, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - S.O.N.G. Sheet: Southern Ontario Newspaper Guild, Toronto, Canada, 1979, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Officers' Report: State, County & Municipal Workers of America, Lansing, MI, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - TIU News / Telecommunications International Union: Telecommunications International Union, Hamden, CT, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Telephone Pioneer: Telephone Pioneers of America, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Big Apple Newsletter: Telephone Pioneers of America/Big Apple Life Member Club, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Laying it on the Line: Telephone Workers, New York, NY, circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Texas AFL-CIO Labor News: Texas AFL-CIO, Austin, TX, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Update: Texas State Employees Union, Austin, TX, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Industrial Leader: The Industrial Leader Publishing Co., Winston-Salem, NC, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - New Lead: Toronto Newspaper Guild, Toronto, Canada, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - True North: True North Communications, Saskatoon, Canada, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Union Advocate: Union Advocate newspaper, Inc., St. Paul, MN, 1992, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Steward Update: Union Communication Services, Inc., Annapolis, MD, 1990-1991, 1994-1996, 2003, undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Dial: United Brotherhood of Telephone Workers, 1939-1940, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Protecting Workers Health and Welfare: United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, Chicago, IL, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Shop News: United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, CIO, Brooklyn, NY, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - UE: United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, circa 1980s (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - United Paperworkers' Corporate Campaign News: United Paperworkers International Union Local 6288, De Pere, WI, circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Photo Flashes: United Photographic Employees - Local Industrial Union #415, New York, NY, 1939 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Arkansas Union Labor Bulletin: United Publishing Co., Little Rock, AK, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - U.T.O. News: Official Journal United Telephone Organizations: United Telephone Organizations, New York, NY, 1949-1958 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Unity Slate: Unity Slate, Levittown, NY, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Inside Story: Vancouver/New Westminster Newspaper Guild, Vancouver, Canada, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild: Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild, circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Guild Forum: Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild Local 35 TNG, AFL-CIO, CLC, Washington, DC, 1978-1981, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Telephone Workers' Outlook: West Virginia Union of Telephone Workers, TWOC-CIO, Charleston, WV, 1948 (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - 17: Wire Service Guild, New York, NY, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Citysplinter: San Francisco, CA, circa 1980s (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Frontpage, 1946-1948, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Label Facts: Middleton, WI, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Miners's Bulletin, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - NABET News: Chicago, Il, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Rank and File Newsletter, 1955, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Times Company Report: New York, NY, 1985 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Union Voice: Bristol, CT, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - UPSurge: Cleveland, OH, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Subseries I.C: Constituency Groups, 1915-2009; 4.75 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 3 oversize flat boxes
    This series collects newsletters and serials issued by organizations representing demographic groups working across different industries, including publications issued by Asian-American organizations and staff groups (Asian Americans for Equal Employment; Chinese Staff and Workers Association); African-American workers (the Black Workers Congress; Coalition of Revolutionary Black Workers; Coalition of Black Trade Unionists); religious organizations (The Workmen's Circle; Histradut); and women's groups (Non-Traditional Employment for Women; Women for Economic Justice; Union Women's Alliance to Gain Equality). Featuring many organizations based in New York City, and largely dating from the 1970s to the 1990s, publications often combine local community news with writing around labor activism, detailing the living and working conditions of factory workers, restaurant staff, and sleeping car porters, among others.
    - Update on Kenya: African-American Labor Center, Washington, DC, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Update on Malawi: African-American Labor Center, Washington, DC, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - WomeNews: AFTRA National Women's Committee, Los Angeles, CA, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - A.S.U. Outlook: American Student Union (CCNY Main Day Chapter), New York, NY, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - APALA, New York Chapter Newsletter: APALA New York Chapter, NY, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Asian Labour Update: Asia Monitor Research Center, Kowloon, Hong Kong, 1990-1992 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - AAFEE Newspaper: Asian Americans for Equal Employment, New York, NY, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Rights: Asian Network for the Rights of Occupational Accident Victims, Hong Kong, China, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - AAFLI News: Asian-American Free Labor Institute, Washington, DC, 1975-1979, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - China Labor Notes: Asian-American Free Labor Institute, Washington, DC, 1990-1993 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Manifesto: Black Workers Congress, Highland Park, MI, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Advance: Black Workers Congress, Detroit, MI, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Point of Production: Black Workers Congress, Detroit, MI, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Siege: Black Workers Congress, Detroit, MI, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Black Worker: Black Workers Council, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Justice Speaks: Black Workers for Justice, Rocky Mount, NC, 1992-2009 (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
    - Detroit to Durban: Black Workers' Common Struggle: Black Workers Organizing Committee/United Front Press, Oakland, CA, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Black Worker: Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters (AFL-CIO, CLC), 1959 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Chinatown Labor Fair programs: Chinese Staff and Workers Association, New York, NY, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Bulletin: Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Spark: Ed Dalton, Dublin, Republic of Ireland, 1915 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Workers' Struggle/La Lucha Obrera: Federation of Puerto Rican Workers, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Chinese-American Workers: Past & Present: an Anthology of Getting Together: Getting Together/I Wor Kuen, San Francisco, CA, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Frente a Frente: Histradut (Confederacion General de los Trabajadores de Israel), Mexico City, Mexico, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - International Committee for the Defense of African Workers (Newsletter): International Committee for the Defense of African Workers, New York, NY, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Labour in Israel: International Department of Histadrut, General Federation of Labour in Israel, Tel-Aviv, Israel, 1985-1989 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Newsletter: International Women's Tribune Centre, Inc., New York, NY, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Iranian-American Labor Solidarity: Iranian-American Labor Solidarity Committee, Los Angeles, CA, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Labour Solidarity: Iranian-Canadian Solidarity Committee, Toronto, Canada, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Solidarieta e Liberta: Italian-American Labor Council News, New York, NY, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Working Women: Korean Women Workers Associations United, Seoul, South Korea, 1997-2003 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Labor's Daily: Labor's Daily, Charleston, WV, 1952-1956 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Working Mother: Maternal Information Services, Inc., New York, NY, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Asian American Network: National Asian American Telecommunications Association, San Francisco, CA, 1985-1994 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Women at Work: National Commission on Working Women and Women's Work Force Network of Wider Opportunities for Women, Washington, DC, 1985-1989 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Women Workers: Some Basic Statistics: New England Free Press, Boston, MA, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - American Labor History: Women in the Working Class: New England Free Press/Radical America, Somerville, MA/Cambridge, MA, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Whither China?: New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Visions: New York Asian Women's Center, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - New York Negro American Labor Council Newsletter: New York Negro American Labor Council, New York, NY, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - NEW'S Letter: Non-Traditional Employment for Women, New York, NY, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Office Workers News: Office Workers of New Haven, New Haven, CT, 1976-1979 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Philippine Labor Alert: Philippine Workers Support Committee, Honolulu, HI, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Solidarity Bulletin/Tygodnik Solidarność: Polish Workers Task Force, League for Industrial Democracy, Poland Watch Center / Committee in Support of Solidarity, Berkeley, CA, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Inner-City Voice: Official Organ of Revolutionary Black Workers: Revolutionary Black Workers, Detroit, MI, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Seattle Union Record: Striking Employees of The Seattle Times, Seattle, WA, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Second Page: Sun Life workers, San Francisco, CA, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Black Workers Forum: Theoretical Journal of the Democratic Workers Party: Synthesis Publications, San Francisco, CA, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Black Workers in Revolt: The Guardian, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Union W.A.G.E.: Union Women's Alliance to Gain Equality, Berkeley, CA, 1973-1978 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7553)
    - Spirit of '76: W.C. Penn South, New York, NY, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Shorter Work-Time News: Women for Economic Justice, Boston, MA, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Working Women: Our Stories and Struggles: Women of the Center for United Labor Action, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Boston Circle-Lite Souvenir Journal: Workmen's Circle, Framingham, MA, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - Culture and Education: Workmen's Circle, New York, NY, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Friend: Workmen's Circle, Passaic, NJ, 1939, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Horizons: Workmen's Circle, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - Inner Circle: Workmen's Circle, New York, NY, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Silver Anniversary: Workmen's Circle, New York, NY, 1952 (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - 1001 Reports: Workmen's Circle - Jack Zukerman Branch 1001, New York, NY, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 65)
    - Jewish Labor Bund Bulletin: World-Coordinating Committee of Bundist and Affiliated Jewish Socialist Organizations, New York, NY, 1947-1949 (Box 27, Folder 66)
    - Young Workers' Liberation League: Young Workers' Liberation League, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 67)
    - Young Fighter: A Paper for Young Workers in Shops and Unions: Youth Committee of the Trade Union Unity Council, New York, NY, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - Subseries I.D: Co-operatives, 1921-2009; 3.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 oversize flat box
    Representing a swell of activity in businesses structured around the co-operative model between 1930-1950, this series collects serials and publications issued by a variety of co-operative organizations -- including farms, factories, markets, distributors, and co-operative leagues -- in the United States. Publications are often instructive, featuring tips on growth or business operation (ECL Leadership Bulletin; Cooperative Builder), commentating on the co-operative economy and advertising products and supplies.
    - Communities: Communities Publications Cooperative, Louisa, VA, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Need for Consumer Cooperation: Consumer Distribution Corporation, New York, NY, circa 1950s (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Cooperative Consumer: Consumers Cooperative Association, Kansas City, MO, 1948-1949, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Trip to Cooperative Europe: Consumers Cooperative Association, North Kansas City, MO, circa 1930s (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Cooperation: Consumers Cooperative Movement, New York, NY, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Consumers' Cooperation: Consumers' Cooperative Movement/Cooperative League of the USA, New York, NY, 1938, 1941-1943 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Co-op Crier: Consumers' Cooperative Services, Inc., New York, NY, 1963-1964, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Co-op News: Co-op Education Guild, Inc., New York, NY, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Co-Op Report: Cooperative League of the USA, Chicago, IL, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Cooperative League News Service: Cooperative League of the USA, New York, NY, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Cooperative News Service: Cooperative League of the USA, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Organized Consumer: Cooperative Publications Committees, New York, NY, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 29)